Ashish Prasad

Digital Strategist, Writer and Speaker. CEO @SOFTRE and DriveSafely.in

Summary

Ashish Prasad is the founder and CEO of SOFTRE, one of the fastest growing digital agencies and also serves as the Director of Drive Safely India. He has worked with businesses and educational institutions responsible for developing and implementing digital engagement strategies.

Apart from this, as a Social Media Influencer, Ashish enjoys penning down his thoughts on a variety of topics on Digital Marketing, Upcoming Technology and keeps up a blog for that. He also frequently reviews books and tech products.

Experience

Consultant at Brand24 Experts Hub at Brand24 January 2017 - Present

Contributor at YourStory Media August 2017 - Present

Founder & CEO at SOFTRE February 2013 - Present

Founder & Director January 2015 - Present

- To lead on issues of road safety and ensuring that the DriveSafely campaign is carried in accordance with best practice and internal procedures making sure that road safety risks are managed properly.
- Responsible for production, editorial direction and casting for the DriveSafely videos.
- Implementation of website, design and development.

Digital Strategist and Consultant January 2017 - Present

Member of the Board of Trustees

June 2015 - Present

Board Trustee at Maruthi Global Trust, which is the governing body of Maruthi International Residential School located at Tumkur, India.

For more information please visit, www.mis.ac.in

Education

Massey University

Ashish Prasad

Digital Strategist, Writer and Speaker. CEO @SOFTRE and DriveSafely.in



Contact Ashish on LinkedIn